



14.08.1993



jonitirkkonenmusic@gmail.com



Tilankuja 8 B 37 01800 Klaukkala



+358 50 559 4488



<u> LinkedIn</u>



<u>GitHub</u>

SKILLS

IT

- Javascript
- HTML5
- CSS
- Java
- MS Office 365
- CCNA 1
- Active Directory
- GIMP
- Audacity
- SAP
- Microsoft Dynamics
- · Social Media

Language

- Finnish Native
- English Professional
- Swedish Fundamentals
- German Fundamentals

JONI TIRKKONEN

PROFILE

I am a first year student of ICT at Haaga-Helia university of applied sciences. I have also studied ICT-engineering for almost two years at Metropolia UAS.

I am looking for a job where I can enhance my skills in ICT and where I get to learn more about different systems. Especially for the summer.

I would be describe myself as an extrovert person and I have already gained experience at working in different kinds of job environments.

WORK EXPERIENCE

09/2007 - (present)

Klaukkalan Rakennustyö

Oy

IT Officer

(Previous title: Logistics

manager).

05/2020 - 11/2020

Palvelukeskus Helsinki

ICT Support Officer

(Technical customer support for ICT solutions provided by the city of Helsinki).

08/2018 - 06/2019

Neste K KannelmäkiGas Station Cashier

05/2017 - 11/2017

SYKES Enterprises Berlin

Technical Customer Support,

Sony

EDUCATION

08/2021 - (12/2024)

08/2018 - 12/2020

Haaga-Helia UAS, Helsinki

ICT, Bachelor of Business

Administration

Metropolia UAS, Espoo

ICT, engineering